<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>{ @Techievena }</title>
		<description>The personal website and blog of Abinash Senapati, undergraduate student @ I.I.T. Kharagpur. Blogging to give an overview of the stuffs I do.....</description>
		<link>https://techievena.github.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://techievena.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Personal Time Machine</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;going-ahead-of-time&quot;&gt;GOING AHEAD OF TIME&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time is the most influential factor in this world. It is abstract. Everything in this world is commanded and decided by time. Nobody can escape the hold of time.&lt;br /&gt;
We all must have read or at-least heard of the all-time classic of H.G. Wells, in which a scientist invents a machine that transports him far into the future where he discovers a changed world inhabited by two unusual races, the Eloi and the Morlocks. From then… or even back, human race has been fantasizing about gaining control over time; because it is the time which gives us the opportunity to make use of it. Those who make best use of time and avail those opportunities grow and rise in life. He is the wisest who makes the best use of time in his hand.&lt;br /&gt;
But what if I say &lt;strong&gt;now you can see your future!!!!&lt;/strong&gt; Sounds kinda interesting right?? Ya it’s true. Now…. with the advancement of modern technologies, we have come to a stage where we can see ahead of time and if required, be prepared for the same. With the recent developments, going on in the sector of AI and machine learning; Now we can forecast what’s going to happen the next day, a day after or even a month after; &lt;strong&gt;all by ourselves.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://techievena.github.io/machine_learning/2016/12/29/personal-time-machine.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://techievena.github.io/machine_learning/2016/12/29/personal-time-machine.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
