<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>{ @Techievena }</title>
		<description>The personal website and blog of Abinash Senapati a.k.a. Techievena.</description>
		<link>https://techievena.github.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://techievena.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Finally.... GSoC!!!</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.opportunitiesforafricans.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/google-summer-of-code-2018-696x414.png&quot; alt=&quot;Google Summer of Code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://techievena.github.io/gsoc/2018/04/28/gsoc_selected.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://techievena.github.io/gsoc/2018/04/28/gsoc_selected.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A Walk with coala</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coala.io&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/7521600/15992701/ef245fd4-30ef-11e6-992d-275c5ca7c3a0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;coala&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://techievena.github.io/gci/2017/04/22/journey.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://techievena.github.io/gci/2017/04/22/journey.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>PYTHON ka DABBA</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-dabba&quot;&gt;THE DABBA&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dabba or the tiffin as called when it was introduced by the British, is so special to all of us. Going to school and waiting for those long hours in classrooms resisting the smell of your mother’s delicious handcooked sabji and ghee ke parathes waiting inside your dabba to be gulped by you and your friends (if apparently you are spared anything by them). As soon as the tiffin break bell rings, remember your friends jumping on you fighting for your dabba. Those were most rejoiced moments of our school days. The dabba was so special!
&lt;img src=&quot;https://github.com/Techievena/Roomzoned/blob/master/docs/dabba.jpg?raw=true&quot; alt=&quot;dabba&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://techievena.github.io/python/2017/01/01/python-package.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://techievena.github.io/python/2017/01/01/python-package.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Personal Time Machine</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;going-ahead-of-time&quot;&gt;GOING AHEAD OF TIME&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time is the most influential factor in this world. It is abstract. Everything in this world is commanded and decided by time. Nobody can escape the hold of time.&lt;br /&gt;
We all must have read or at-least heard of the all-time classic of H.G. Wells, in which a scientist invents a machine that transports him far into the future where he discovers a changed world inhabited by two unusual races, the Eloi and the Morlocks. From then… or even back, human race has been fantasizing about gaining control over time; because it is the time which gives us the opportunity to make use of it. Those who make best use of time and avail those opportunities grow and rise in life. He is the wisest who makes the best use of time in his hand.&lt;br /&gt;
But what if I say &lt;strong&gt;now you can see your future!!!!&lt;/strong&gt; Sounds kinda interesting right?? Ya it’s true. Now…. with the advancement of modern technologies, we have come to a stage where we can see ahead of time and if required, be prepared for the same. With the recent developments, going on in the sector of AI and machine learning; Now we can forecast what’s going to happen the next day, a day after or even a month after; &lt;strong&gt;all by ourselves.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://techievena.github.io/machine_learning/2016/12/29/personal-time-machine.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://techievena.github.io/machine_learning/2016/12/29/personal-time-machine.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
